(Howard:)Gentlemen, switching
to local nerd news...
...Fishman, Chen, Chaudury and McNair
aren't fielding a team...
...in the Physics Bowl this year.
- You're kidding. Why not?
- They formed a barbershop quartet...
(Howard:)...and got a gig playing
Knott's Berry Farm.
(Penny:)Wow. So in your world,
you're like the cool guys.
Recognize.
This is our year. With those guys out...
(Leonard:)...the entire Physics Bowl
will kneel before Zod.
- Zod?
- Kryptonian villain. Long story.
(Raj:)Good story.
(Sheldon:)- Count me out.
- What? Why?
(Sheldon:)You want me to use my intelligence
in a tawdry competition?
(Sheldon:)Would you ask Picasso
to play Pictionary?
(Sheldon:)Would you ask Noah Webster
to play Boggle?
(Sheldon:)Would you ask Jacques Cousteau
to play Go Fish?
Come on, you need a four-person team.
We're four people.
(Sheldon:)By that reasoning we should also
play bridge, hold up a huppah...
(Sheldon:)...and enter the Olympic bobsled
competition.
(Penny:)Tickets to that, please.
Sheldon, what? Do I need to quote
Spock's dying words to you?
(Sheldon:)No, don't.
"The needs of the many..."
"Outweigh the needs of the few..."
"Or the one."
Damn it, I'll do it.